Guide to the Pat Williams Papers 1979-1997
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- General Correspondence, 1979-1996; Series I; 21.5 linear feet and 3.5 linear feet microfiche
  - Subseries 2: Form Letter Text
    - Form Letter Text, 1988 (Box-folder 29/1)
    - Form Letter Text, 1988 (Box-folder 29/2)
    - Form Letter Text, 1988 (Box-folder 29/3)
    - Form Letter Text, 1988 (Box-folder 29/4)
    - Form Letter Text, 1988 (Box-folder 29/5)
    - Form Letter Text, 1988 (Box-folder 29/6)
    - Form Letter Text, 1989 (Box-folder 29/7)
    - Form Letter Text, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 30/1)
    - Form Letter Text, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 30/2)
    - Form Letter Text, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 30/3)
    - Form Letter Text, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 30/4)
    - Form Letter Text, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 30/5)
    - Form Letter Text, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 30/6)
    - Form Letter Text, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 31/1)
    - Form Letter Text, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 31/2)
    - Form Letter Text, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 31/3)
    - Form Letter Text, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 31/4)
    - Form Letter Drafts, 1988 (Box-folder 31/5)
    - Form Letter Drafts, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 31/6)
    - Form Letter Drafts, 1991 (Box-folder 31/7)
    - Form Letter Drafts, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 32/1)
    - Form Letter Drafts, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 32/2)
    - Form Letter Drafts, 1985 (Box-folder 32/3)
    - Form Letter Drafts, 1985 (Box-folder 32/4)
    - Form Letter Drafts, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 32/5)
    - Form Letter Drafts, 1985 (Box-folder 32/6)
    - Form Letter Drafts, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 33/1)
    - Form Letter Drafts, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 33/2)
  - Subseries 3: Messages and Invitations
    - Christmas Cards, 1979-1996 (Box-folder 34/1)
    - Condolences, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 34/2)
    - Condolences, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 34/3)
    - Condolences, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 34/4)
    - Condolences, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 34/5)
    - Congratulations, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 34/6)
    - Congratulations, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 34/7)
    - Congratulations, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 35/1)
    - Congratulations, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 35/2)
    - Congratulations, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 35/3)
    - Congratulations, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 35/4)
    - Congratulations, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 35/5)
    - Get Well, 1983-1996 (Box-folder 35/6)
    - Invitations and Placecards, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 36/1)
    - Invitations and Placecards, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 36/2)
    - Invitations and Placecards, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 36/3)
    - Invitations and Placecards, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 36/4)
    - Invitations and Placecards, 1986 (Box-folder 36/5)
    - Invitations and Placecards, 1987 (Box-folder 36/6)
    - Invitations and Placecards, 1988 (Box-folder 36/7)
    - Invitations and Placecards, 1989 (Box-folder 36/8)
    - Invitations and Placecards, 1990 (Box-folder 37/1)
    - Invitations and Placecards, 1991 (Box-folder 37/2)
    - Invitations, 1991 (Box-folder 37/3)
    - Invitations and Placecards, 1992 (Box-folder 37/4)
    - Invitations, 1992 (Box-folder 37/5)
    - Invitations and Placecards, 1993 (Box-folder 37/6)
    - Invitations, 1993 (Box-folder 38/1)
    - Invitations and Placecards, 1994 (Box-folder 38/2)
    - Invitations, 1994 (Box-folder 38/3)
    - Invitations and Placecards, 1995 (Box-folder 38/4)
    - Invitations, 1995 (Box-folder 38/5)
    - Invitations and Placecards, 1996 (Box-folder 38/6)
    - Placecards, 1997-1999 and undated (Box-folder 38/7)
    - Messages, 1981 (Box-folder 39/1)
    - Messages, 1982 (Box-folder 39/2)
    - Messages, 1983 (Box-folder 39/3)
    - Messages, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 39/4)
    - Messages, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 39/5)
    - Messages, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 39/6)
  - Subseries 4: Personal Congressional
    - 1983-1986 (Box-folder 40/1)
    - 1987-1988 (Box-folder 40/2)
    - 1990 (Box-folder 40/3)
    - 1991-1992 (Box-folder 40/4)
    - 1993 (Box-folder 40/5)
    - 1994 (Box-folder 40/6)
    - 1995-1996 (Box-folder 41/1)
    - Thank You, 1983 (Box-folder 41/2)
    - Thank You, 1984 (Box-folder 41/3)
    - Thank You, 1985 (Box-folder 41/4)
    - Thank You, 1986 (Box-folder 42/1)
    - Thank You, 1987 (Box-folder 42/2)
    - Thank You, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 42/3)
    - Thank You, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 42/4)
    - Thank You, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 42/5)
    - Thank You, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 42/6)
  - Subseries 5: Newsletter and Questionnaire
    - 1979-1980 (Box-folder 43/1)
    - 1981-1982 (Box-folder 43/2)
    - 1983-1984 (Box-folder 43/3)
    - 1985-1986 (Box-folder 43/4)
    - 1987-1988 (Box-folder 43/5)
    - 1989-1990 (Box-folder 43/6)
    - 1991-1992 (Box-folder 43/7)
    - 1993-1994 (Box-folder 43/8)
    - 1995-1996 (Box-folder 43/9)
  - Subseries 6: Personal Constituent
    - 96th-99th Congress A-Go, 1979-1987 (Box 44)
    - 96th-99th Congress Go-O, 1979-1987 (Box 45)
    - 96th-99th Congress O'N-Z, 1979-1987 (Box 46)
    - 99th-102nd Congress A-Ha, 1987-1993 (Box 47)
    - 99th-102nd Congress Hag-Ru, 1987-1993 (Box 48)
    - 99th-102nd Congress Ru-Z, 1987-1993 (Box 49)
    - 103rd-104th Congress A-Z, 1993-1997 (Box 50)
- Legislative, 1979-1996; Series II; 22.5 linear feet
  This series consists of the materials that Williams' office collected and generated in the course of legislative activities. The files include publications, notes, memorandums, issue-related correspondence, voting records, and the bills that Williams introduced.
  The series is subdivided into fifteen subseries: Agriculture, Bills Introduced, Budget, Education, Energy, Environment, Health Social Service and Women, Labor, Legislative Profiles, Legislative Activity Guide, Montana, National Endowment for the Arts, Native American Issues, Transportation, and Voting Record. Within these categories, materials arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Subseries 1: Agriculture
    - Agricultural Research Center, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 51/1)
    - Barley Payments, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 51/2)
    - Bioscience, 1987-1994 (Box-folder 51/3)
    - Brucellosis, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 51/4)
    - BN-ATSF, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 51/5)
    - Canadian Grain, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 51/6)
    - Crop Insurance, 1994 (Box-folder 51/7)
    - Crop Insurance, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 52/1)
    - Conservation Reserve Program (CRP), 1994-1996 (Box-folder 52/2)
    - Conservation Reserve Program (CRP), 1994-1996 (Box-folder 52/3)
    - Conservation Reserve Program (CRP), 1994-1996 (Box-folder 52/4)
    - Conservation Reserve Program (CRP), 1994-1996 (Box-folder 52/5)
    - Equipment, 1996 (Box-folder 52/6)
    - Farm Bill, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 52/7)
    - Farm Bill, 1996 (Box-folder 53/1)
    - Grain Car Shortage, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 53/2)
    - Grazing, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 53/3)
    - Grazing, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 53/4)
    - ITC, 1994 (Box-folder 53/5)
    - Missouri River Flow, 1996 (Box-folder 53/6)
    - Power Marketing Agencies, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 53/7)
    - Whirling Disease, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 53/8)
  - Subseries 2: Bills Introduced
    - 96th Congress, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 54/1)
    - 97th Congress, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 54/2)
    - 98th Congress, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 54/3)
    - 99th Congress, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 54/4)
    - 100th Congress, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 54/5)
    - 101st Congress, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 54/6)
    - 102nd Congress, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 55/1)
    - 103rd Congress, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 55/2)
    - 103rd Congress, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 55/3)
    - 104th Congress, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 55/4)
    - 104th Congress, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 55/5)
    - Ethics issues, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 55/6)
  - Subseries 3: Budget
    - Balanced Budget, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 56/1)
    - Campaign Finance Reform, 1993 (Box-folder 56/2)
    - Education Budget Hearing, 1983 (Box-folder 56/3)
    - Education Budget Hearing, 1983 (Box-folder 56/4)
    - Education Budget Hearing, 1983 (Box-folder 56/5)
    - Education Budget Hearing, 1983 (Box-folder 56/6)
    - Education Budget Hearing, 1983 (Box-folder 56/7)
    - PILT, 1994 (Box-folder 56/8)
    - PILT, undated (Box-folder 56/9)
    - Testimony, 1979-1987 (Box-folder 56/10)
  - Subseries 4: Education
    - Belmount Group Defaults, 1986-1996 (Box-folder 57/1)
    - Careers Act/Conference, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 57/2)
    - Careers Act/Floor Action, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 57/3)
    - Careers Act/Committee, 1995 (Box-folder 57/4)
    - Education of the Handicapped, 1986 (Box-folder 57/5)
    - Higher Education/Background, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 57/6)
    - Higher Education/Background, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 57/7)
    - Higher Education/Background, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 57/8)
    - Irish Children's Bill, 1993 (Box-folder 58/1)
    - Libraries, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 58/2)
    - Middle Income Student Assistance, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 58/3)
    - Montana Education Association, 1978-1996 (Box-folder 58/4)
    - Montana Higher Education Restructuring, 1994 (Box-folder 58/5)
    - Museum of the Rockies, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 58/6)
    - National Board of Prof. Standards, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 58/7)
    - National Summit on Education, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 58/8)
    - Rural Schools, 1978-1994 (Box-folder 58/9)
    - Sallie Mae, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 58/10)
    - Student Aid Cuts, 1995 (Box-folder 59/1)
    - Student Defaults, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 59/2)
    - Summit, 1983 (Box-folder 59/3)
    - Title IX, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 59/4)
    - Tribal Colleges, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 59/5)
    - White House Conference on Libraries, 1991 (Box-folder 59/6)
  - Subseries 5: Energy
    - Flint Creek Dam, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 60/1)
    - Gwen Nuclear Towers, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 60/2)
    - Kerr Dam, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 60/3)
    - Middle Creek Dam, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 60/4)
    - Mission Valley Power, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 60/5)
    - NCAT, 1987-1994 (Box-folder 60/6)
    - Northern Tier Pipeline, 1979 (Box-folder 60/7)
    - Dick Sloan Power, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 60/8)
    - Plasma Arc, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 60/9)
    - Power Planning Act, 1980 (Box-folder 60/10)
    - Rhone Poulenc, 1995 (Box-folder 60/11)
    - Tongue River Railroad Project, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 61/1)
    - Tongue River Railroad Project, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 61/2)
    - Tongue River Railroad Project, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 61/3)
    - Kerr Dam, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 61/4)
    - Libby Dam, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 61/5)
    - WAPA, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 61/6)
  - Subseries 6: Environment
    - BLM Building, 1995 (Box-folder 62/1)
    - BLM Building, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 62/2)
    - Bitter Root Irrigators, 1991 (Box-folder 62/3)
    - Black Footed Ferrets, 1992 (Box-folder 62/4)
    - Hungry Horse Dam, 1993 (Box-folder 62/5)
    - Butte Water l, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 62/6)
    - Canyon Ferry, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 62/7)
    - Canyon Ferry, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 62/8)
    - Capital Gains Wood Lots, 1989 (Box-folder 62/9)
    - Columbia Falls, 1995 (Box-folder 62/10)
    - Como Dam, 1992 (Box-folder 62/11)
    - Cultural Resource Libby Dam, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 62/12)
    - Drinking Water, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 62/13)
    - Flathead Indian Irrigation Project, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 62/14)
    - Fire Season, 1994 (Box-folder 62/15)
    - Fort Peck, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 62/16)
    - Forest Service Regulations, 1994 (Box-folder 63/1)
    - Gallatin Land Exchange, 1993 (Box-folder 63/2)
    - Glacier Park Chalets, 1993 (Box-folder 63/3)
    - Glacier Park, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 63/4)
    - Heritage Areas, 1996 (Box-folder 63/5)
    - Hunting/Wildlife Refuges, 1992 (Box-folder 63/6)
    - Koocanusa, 1994 (Box-folder 63/7)
    - Libby Land Exchange, 1982-1994 (Box-folder 63/8)
    - Log Exports, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 63/9)
    - Lonesome Lake Policy, 1994 (Box-folder 63/10)
    - Underground Storage System, 1999 (Box-folder 63/11)
    - Metcalf Refuge, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 64/1)
    - Mining Reform, 1993 (Box-folder 64/2)
    - Missouri River, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 64/3)
    - John Mumma, undated (Box-folder 64/4)
    - Old Faithful Protection Act, 1993 (Box-folder 64/5)
    - Old Faithful Protection Act, 1993 (Box-folder 64/6)
    - Park Overflights, 1994 (Box-folder 65/1)
    - Park Overflights (HR 4163), 1994 (Box-folder 65/2)
    - Peace Foundation Amendment, 1994 (Box-folder 65/3)
    - Petes Hill, 1992 (Box-folder 65/4)
    - Public Land Access Hearing, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 65/5)
    - Reforestation, 1982-1989 (Box-folder 65/6)
    - Rock Creek, 1994 (Box-folder 65/7)
    - Ski Area Fees, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 65/8)
    - Superior, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 65/9)
    - Sweet Grass Hills, 1993 (Box-folder 65/10)
    - USFS Forestry Museum, 1994 (Box-folder 65/11)
    - Virginia City Preservation, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 65/12)
    - Wood Product Center, 1989 (Box-folder 65/13)
    - Wolf Reintroduction, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 65/14)
    - EPA Warm Springs Pond, 1994 (Box-folder 65/15)
    - Bob Marshall Wilderness, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 66/1)
    - Bob Marshall Wilderness, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 66/2)
    - Bob Marshall Wilderness, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 66/3)
    - Bob Marshall Wilderness, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 66/4)
    - Bob Marshall Wilderness, 1981 (Box-folder 66/5)
    - Bob Marshall Wilderness, 1981 (Box-folder 66/6)
  - Subseries 7: Health, Social Service, and Women
    - Abortion, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 67/1)
    - Aging, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 67/2)
    - Clinton's Pension Reform, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 67/3)
    - Developmental Disabilities, 1986-1995 (Box-folder 67/4)
    - Employer/Employee Relations Act, 1995 (Box-folder 67/5)
    - ERISA, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 67/6)
    - Equal Rights Amendment, 1980-1996 (Box-folder 67/7)
    - Great Falls Hospital, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 67/8)
    - Harris Trust, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 67/9)
    - Health Reform, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 67/10)
    - Health Reform, 1994 (Box-folder 68/1)
    - Health Reform, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 68/2)
    - Health Deductible/Self Employed, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 68/3)
    - Housing, Affordable, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 68/4)
    - Juvenile Justice, 1979-1996 (Box-folder 68/5)
    - Kennedey Kassebaum, 1996 (Box-folder 68/6)
    - Low Income Housing, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 68/7)
    - Medicaid/Medicare, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 68/8)
    - Medical Savings Accounts, undated (Box-folder 68/9)
    - Mental Health, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 68/10)
    - Montana Health Issues, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 68/11)
    - Native American Health, 1996 (Box-folder 68/12)
    - Migrant Health Care, 1996 (Box-folder 69/1)
    - Pension Benefits Guaranty, 1995 (Box-folder 69/2)
    - Physicians Association, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 69/3)
    - Provider Sponsored Networks, 1995 (Box-folder 69/4)
    - Reforming Welfare, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 69/5)
    - Reforming Welfare, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 69/6)
    - Reforming Welfare, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 69/7)
    - Reforming Welfare, 1995 (Box-folder 69/8)
    - Jeanette Rankin Statue, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 70/1)
    - Jeanette Rankin Statue, 1985 (Box-folder 70/2)
    - Jeanette Rankin Statue, 1985 (Box-folder 70/3)
    - Jeanette Rankin Statue, 1985 (Box-folder 70/4)
    - Jeanette Rankin Statue, 1985 (Box-folder 70/5)
    - Rural Health, 1994 (Box-folder 71/1)
    - Rural Health, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 71/2)
    - Seniors, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 71/3)
    - Social Security Benefits Statements, 1995 (Box-folder 71/4)
    - Women's Issues, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 71/5)
    - Workers Compensation, 1994 (Box-folder 71/6)
    - Womens Education and Equity Act, 1984 (Box-folder 71/7)
  - Subseries 8: Labor
    - Boxing, 1966-1988 (Box-folder 72/1)
    - Boxing, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 72/2)
    - Boxing, 1985 (Box-folder 72/3)
    - Boxing, 1983-1996 (Box-folder 72/4)
    - Boxing, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 72/5)
    - Boxing Council, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 72/6)
    - Baseball Strike, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 72/7)
    - Electronic Monitoring, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 73/1)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1994 (Box-folder 73/2)
    - Management Subcommittee, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 73/3)
    - Polygraph Protection, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 73/4)
    - Rhone-Poulenc, 1995 (Box-folder 73/5)
    - OSHA, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 73/6)
    - Temporary Federal Employment, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 73/7)
    - Temporary Federal Employment, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 73/8)
    - Temporary Federal Employment, 1992 (Box-folder 73/9)
  - Subseries 9: Legislative Profiles
    - Jan. 5-Mar. 3, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 74/1)
    - Mar. 4-Oct. 16, 1986 (Box-folder 74/2)
    - Jan. 6-April, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 74/3)
    - May-Dec, 1988 (Box-folder 74/4)
    - Jan. 3-Mar, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 74/5)
    - Apr-Oct, 1990 (Box-folder 74/6)
    - Jan-Sep, 1991 (Box-folder 74/7)
    - Oct-Mar, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 74/8)
    - Jan-Oct, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 74/9)
  - Subseries 10: Legislative Activity Guide
    - 99th Congress, 1986 (Box-folder 75/1)
    - 99th Congress, 1986 (Box-folder 75/2)
    - 99th Congress, 1986 (Box-folder 75/3)
    - 99th Congress, 1986 (Box-folder 75/4)
    - 99th Congress, 1986 (Box-folder 75/5)
    - 99th Congress, 1986 (Box-folder 75/6)
    - 100th Congress 1st Session, 1987 (Box-folder 75/7)
    - 100th Congress 1st Session, 1987 (Box-folder 75/8)
    - 100th Congress 1st Session, 1987 (Box-folder 75/9)
    - 100th Congress 2nd Session, 1988 (Box-folder 75/10)
    - 100th Congress 2nd Session, 1988 (Box-folder 76/1)
    - 100th Congress 2nd Session, 1988 (Box-folder 76/2)
    - 101st Congress, 1989 (Box-folder 76/3)
    - 101st Congress, 1989 (Box-folder 76/4)
    - 101st Congress, 1989 (Box-folder 76/5)
    - 101st Congress, 1989 (Box-folder 76/6)
    - 101st Congress, 1989 (Box-folder 76/7)
    - 102nd Congress, 1991 (Box-folder 76/8)
    - 102nd Congress, 1991 (Box-folder 77/1)
    - 102nd Congress, 1992 (Box-folder 77/2)
    - 102nd Congress, 1992 (Box-folder 77/3)
    - 102nd Congress, 1992 (Box-folder 77/4)
    - 103rd Congress, 1994 (Box-folder 77/5)
    - 103rd Congress, 1994 (Box-folder 77/6)
    - 104th Congress, 1995 (Box-folder 78/1)
    - 104th Congress, 1995 (Box-folder 78/2)
    - 104th Congress, 1995 (Box-folder 78/3)
    - 104th Congress, 1996 (Box-folder 78/4)
    - 104th Congress, 1996 (Box-folder 78/5)
  - Subseries 11: Montana
    - Aviation Gore Commission, 1986 (Box-folder 79/1)
    - Beaverhead Development Group, 1992 (Box-folder 79/2)
    - Beneficial Use Tax, 1992 (Box-folder 79/3)
    - Champion Lumber, 1989-1993 (Box-folder 79/4)
    - Freemen of Montana, 1996 (Box-folder 79/5)
    - Glendive Veterans Home, 1993 (Box-folder 79/6)
    - Malstrom Air Force Base, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 79/7)
    - Malstrom Air Force Base, 1995 (Box-folder 79/8)
    - Malstrom Air Force Base, 1982-1995 (Box-folder 79/9)
    - McLaughlin Research Institute, 1990 (Box-folder 80/1)
    - Montana Militia, 1995 (Box-folder 80/2)
    - Montana Militia, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 80/3)
    - Montana Department of Commerce, Census Lawsuit, 1991 (Box-folder 80/4)
    - Montana Department of Commerce, Census Lawsuit, 1991 (Box-folder 80/5)
    - Midgetman Missile, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 81/1)
    - Montana Issues, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 81/2)
    - Ross Electric Facility, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 81/3)
    - Superior Mill, 1994 (Box-folder 81/4)
    - Superior Mill, 1994 (Box-folder 81/5)
    - Unabomber, 1996 (Box-folder 81/6)
    - Virginia City, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 81/7)
    - Wade Bomar Bill, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 81/8)
  - Subseries 12: National Endowment for the Arts
    - Background, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 82/1)
    - Background, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 82/2)
    - Background, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 82/3)
    - Background, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 82/4)
    - Background, 1993 (Box-folder 82/5)
    - Background, 1993 (Box-folder 83/1)
    - Background, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 83/2)
    - Background, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 83/3)
    - Background, 1990 (Box-folder 83/4)
    - Background, 1990 (Box-folder 83/5)
    - Background, 1990 (Box-folder 83/6)
    - Background, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 83/7)
    - Background, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 83/8)
    - Background, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 84/1)
    - Background, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 84/2)
    - Background, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 84/3)
    - Background, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 84/4)
    - Background, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 84/5)
    - Background, 1995 (Box-folder 85/1)
    - Background, 1995 (Box-folder 85/2)
    - Background, 1995 (Box-folder 85/3)
    - Background, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 85/4)
    - Background, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 85/5)
    - Amendments, 1990 (Box-folder 85/6)
    - Armey Amendments, 1993 (Box-folder 85/7)
    - Amendments (floor book), 1993 (Box-folder 86/1)
    - Art Summit, 1990 (Box-folder 86/2)
    - Committee Report, 1993 (Box-folder 86/3)
    - Floor Statements and Speeches, undated (Box-folder 86/4)
    - Finley Lawsuit, 1993 (Box-folder 86/5)
    - Funding, 1990 (Box-folder 86/6)
    - Gunderson Amendment, 1993 (Box-folder 86/7)
    - Hunter, Baucus, Miller, 1993 (Box-folder 86/8)
    - Independent Commission, 1990 (Box-folder 86/9)
    - Individual Artists, 1993 (Box-folder 86/10)
    - Legal Arguments, 1990 (Box-folder 86/11)
    - Letters from Fund Recipients, 1993 (Box-folder 86/12)
    - National Arts Media List, 1995 (Box-folder 86/13)
    - Newsclips, 1990 (Box-folder 86/14)
    - Restrictions and Censorships, undated (Box-folder 87/1)
    - Robert Dornana Letter, 1993 (Box-folder 87/2)
    - Pat Williams Statement, 1993 (Box-folder 87/3)
    - Rules HR4825, 1990 (Box-folder 87/4)
    - Whip Information, 1990 (Box-folder 87/5)
    - Regula Amendment, 1990 (Box-folder 87/6)
  - Subseries 13: Native American Issues
    - Alcohol and Drugs, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 88/1)
    - American Indian Religious Freedom, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 88/2)
    - American Indian Religious Freedom, 1993 (Box-folder 88/3)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs, 1986-1994 (Box-folder 88/4)
    - Bison Range, 1985-1995 (Box-folder 88/5)
    - Blackfeet Hospital, 1978-1987 (Box-folder 88/6)
    - CETA, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 88/7)
    - Cheyenne Health Center, 1996 (Box-folder 88/8)
    - Citizens Hearing on Indian Housing, 1981 (Box-folder 88/9)
    - Federal Magistrate, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 88/10)
    - Gaming Issues, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 88/11)
    - Impact Aide, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 88/12)
    - Indian Gaming Regulation, 1995 (Box-folder 89/1)
    - Indian HUD Housing, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 89/2)
    - Indian Trust Funds, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 89/3)
    - Lame Deer School, 1994 (Box-folder 89/4)
    - Lame Deer School, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 89/5)
    - Lame Deer School, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 89/6)
    - Lame Deer School, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 89/7)
    - Lame Deer School, 1996 (Box-folder 89/8)
    - Lame Deer School, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 89/9)
    - The Little Big Horn, 1993 (Box-folder 89/10)
    - Little Shell Tribe, 1984-1996 (Box-folder 90/1)
    - 107th Meridian, 1984-1995 (Box-folder 90/2)
    - Pat's Successes, 1981-1996 (Box-folder 90/3)
    - President Reagan's Letter, 1981 (Box-folder 90/4)
    - Tribal Appropriations, 1996 (Box-folder 90/5)
    - Tribal Colleges, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 90/6)
    - Yellowstone Bison, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 90/7)
    - Yellowstone Bison, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 90/8)
  - Subseries 14: Transportation
    - Amtrak, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 91/1)
    - BN Railroads, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 91/2)
    - Essential Air Service, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 91/3)
    - FAA Forum, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 91/4)
    - Flight Service Stations, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 91/5)
    - Highway 191, 1986-1993 (Box-folder 91/6)
    - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 91/7)
    - Milwaukee Railroad, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 91/8)
    - Montana Rail Link, 1979 (Box-folder 91/9)
    - Burlington Northern, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 91/10)
    - Burlington Northern, undated (Box-folder 92/1)
    - Burlington Northern, undated (Box-folder 92/2)
  - Subseries 15: Voting Record
    - 96th Congress, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 93/1)
    - 96th Congress, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 93/2)